



Personal Summary

I am an individual who strives for development and success, by implementing my current skills, to expand myself in any working environment. I carry workload with an all round positive attitude, striving to work to reach my targets, whilst simultaneously executing any tasks with extreme attention to detail. I am very approachable, and am able to work well individually, or as part of a team. With experience in both Office and customer service working environments, I have the ability to use strong communication skills with colleagues, clients, and suppliers whether via phone, emails, face to face and/or in meetings in a professional manner.

Key Skills and Competencies

I have developed a variety of skills since commencing my first role in a working environment. These skills include but certainly not limited to, are:

- Having the capability of working under pressure, and meeting strict deadlines
- Executing any tasks with close attention to detail
- Organisational skills such as time management, paperwork, documentation and spreadsheets
- Handling large amounts of paperwork and data
- Handling cash, and management tasks
- Communication with clients/colleagues etc. via all forms of media
- Ability to self teach foreign programs, with correct motivation
- Quick and enthusiastic to learn about how systems work in any working environment
- Working individually and in teams efficiently

Career Summary

*December 2020 - Current*Maternity leave

May 2018 - 2021

Clarendon Homes - Baulkham Hills - Draftsperson

- Draftsperson in the drafting department with an all rounder role covering the work of Tender drawings, Council Developer feedback, compliance check, lodgement drawings, and variation amendments.
- Close contact with Customer sales consultants, Permits team and Estimators
- Problem solving design layouts to suit clients specifications and council regulations
- 2D shadow Diagrams, 2D elevational shadows
- Checking drawings drawn from external contractors
- Hydraulic co-ordinating
- CAD Program Autocad

February 2017 - 2018

Metricon Homes - Baulkham Hills - Draftsperson

- Drafter in the drafting department looking after Contract variations and lodgement plans
- Close contact with Customer sales consultants and Estimators
- Problem solving design layouts to suit clients specifications and council regulations

- 2D shadow Diagrams
- Assisting with the Drafting Inbox and Administration
- Ordering 149 Certificates and sending out jobs to contractors
- CAD Program Autocad

May 2015

ITE Group Plc - London NW6 6RG

- Administration duties, assisting Office Manager and Finance Directors
- Updating Powerpoint presentations to suit mark ups
- Printing final copies of presentation, and producing binded documentation of the presentations
- Receptionist duties such as answering telephone calls, using switchboard to direct calls
- · Being presentable and professional whilst greeting other guests and staff

April 2012-February 2015

Ausco Modular, Seven Hills - Drafter/Estimator

Ausco Modular is a leading provider of modular, relocatable, portable and transportable buildings across Australia. With over 16,000 hire buildings, manufacturing facilities across 4 strategic locations and 17 branches servicing customers Australia wide, Ausco Modular provides hire or purchase solutions across a number of sectors including Mining & Energy, Healthcare, Education, Building & Construction, Commercial & Industrial and Government.

- Drafter/Estimator on a one person team in the Design and Estimating sector, Sydney state branch office
- First stage concept design working with projects either on Hire or Sale buildings, liaising with the sales team, and clients.
- Main Drafter/estimator in first stages of projects, creating and designing floor plans and layouts to suit modular design.
- Liaising with suppliers, and manufacturers when project has been won, seeking service and products at best prices. Eg. Plumbing, steel, electricians and carpentry.
- Close contact with the Design and Estimating team in the Brisbane state and South Australia branch.
- Creating working drawings for clients using 3D modelling software Revit
- Company had adopted Revit the last few years, and originally we have been creating working drawings with Autocad
- Designing floor plans to suit clients specifications and council regulations
- Designing portable buildings such as toilets, offices, camp sites, kitchens, conference rooms, first aid rooms etc.
- Using correct BCA and Australian Standards and specifications
- Travelling on site for inspections, meeting clients, and interstate training
- Estimating overall building costs, using the companies own estimating program "Oscar"
- Creating sales drawings and preliminary working drawings for the client
- Working in tight deadlines
- Site visits to existing buildings to record any changes as to working drawings
- Chair person of 2014 for the health and Safety meetings

August 2011

Mirvac/ Margaret St, Wynyard - 1 week Casual On-call employee

- CAD Technician, updating drawing plans daily using Revit (CAD software)
- Interacting with Design team and other design sectors
- Working on projects simultaneously using BIM (Building Information Modelling)
- Printing out scaled working drawings

May 2011 - April 2012

GUESS/ Pitt St Mall Casual Sales Assistant.

- Greeting and Acknowledging customers
- Organising the shops appearance, by arranging and sorting out apparel
- Paying close attention to customers needs
- Promoting sales with confidence, and knowledge of product
- Being presentable, friendly and approachable
- Cash handling

December 2010 - February 2011

HUGO BOSS / David Jones Casual Sales Assistant.

- Greeting and Acknowledging customers
- Organising the shops appearance, by arranging and sorting out apparel
- Paying close attention to customers needs
- Promoting sales with confidence, and knowledge of product
- Being presentable, friendly and approachable
- Cash handling
- Up selling and adding on products
- Measuring customers for tailored apparel

July 2009 - Septemer 2009

Kue-S services - Casual quantity surveyor Assistant.

Kue-S services is a quantity surveying, home business. Shifts on call, 9-5

My role included:

- Reading and working on architectural drawing plans
- Manually measuring drawing plans with specific tools
- Working with numbers, and large amount of paper work
- Measuring quantities of walls, carpets, concrete, landscaping, materials, finishes etc.
- Using the program Buildsoft that help calculate and help perform the Bill of Quantities.
- The project were mainly schools, housing and apartments.
- Working around the jobs specifications
- Calculating and estimating the price of a building
- Site visits, which include heading out on site, meeting with builders, and working through the site with working drawings. Taking photographs and using them as a guide for the, working drawings.
- Answering telephone calls, and making telephone calls

March 2008 - September 2009

Bright Eyes/ Sunglass Hut - Casual Sales Assistant.

- Working in a retail environment, selling sunglasses, dealing with deliveries and orders, and customer service. Shifts are mostly individual and working alone in store, carrying out manager duties such as:
 - Opening and Closing procedures
 - Cash handling
 - Receiving Telephone calls and emails
 - Ordering and receiving stock
 - Product knowledge
 - Customer service
 - Banking

September 2006 - September 2008

Anz Stadium (Sodexo) - Casual Cashier

Casual worker In the food retail department. Working for large events such as football, soccer games and concerts. Responsibilities include:

- Cash handling
- Customer service
- Cooking food
- Cleaning

December 2007

The Body Shop

Working as a Christmas Casual for around a month for a beauty store. Responsibilities include:

- Customer service
- Product knowledge
- Organising and arranging displays
- Cash handling
- Point of Sale

April 2004 - March 2008

New Zealand Natural

Working as a Casual worker in food retail for four years. I was put in charge of the store in later years and was held responsible for manager roles when the manager was away. Responsibilities include:

- Cash handling
- Customer service
- Banking
- Ordering stock

Receiving telephone calls

Academic Qualifications

- Bachelor of Architectural Computing 2012 Architectural Computing at University of New South Wales, Kensington (incomplete)
- February to June 2009 Advanced Diploma of Architectural Technology at Ultimo TAFE, Sydney.
- 2007 to 2008 Diploma of Architectural Technology. 1st year completed at St George TAFE, Kogarah. 2nd year completed at Ultimo TAFE, Sydney.
- High School Certificate 2006
- Opening and closing procedures

Interests and Activities

- Architecture and Art
- Music
- Travelling
- Gym
- Salsa and Latin dance

